Vladimir Todorović

UI DESIGNER / FRONTEND DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Hi, my name is Vladimir Todorovic, a graduated graphic designer, I live and work in Belgrade.

Previously I worked logos, corporate materials, and prepress for digital printing, until I got into web design and coding.

Now I am deeply involved in building frontend's of web applications. I am dedicated to resolve the issue of user applications, and to created better one.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UPWORK

Frontend developer, UI designer , September 2016 - Current

https://www.upwork.com/o/profiles/users/~0105fab96d0924a21b/

SET plus plus d.o.o.

Web Designer, Jun 2015 - Present (11 months)

Redesign of the Information System SIMA, from the zero point. Also coding html and css templates for various pages.

SIMA is an information system developed as an internal need of construction company SET d.o.o. The project itself has expanded far more than expected and has grown its expectations.

IS SIMA relies on two grounds. One has decades of experience in the business management of private and public companies, while others are contemporary and above all open technologies. http://setpp.rs/en

INFOBIP, Mobile Payment

Web Designer, August 2013 – August 2014 , 1 year and 1 month

Creating mockups, UI and UX solutions for Centili Mobile Payment. Creating design solutions for the Centili Payment Widget, Centili Finance Panel, YCoins - Virtual Currency for Japan, Mobile Payment Widget (Windows Phone, IPhone, Android). Also coding and bug fixing for IE7, IE8, IE9, IE10, IE11, Chrome, Firefox, Safari, Opera, and all mobile browsers.

Working with marketing team. Creating marketing campaign codes. Creating email templates. Working in mailchimp.

WEB BAY SOLUTIONS

Web Designer, Jun 2013 - Jun 2013

I was on practical work, and there I met with the CMS TYPO3.

LABNET

Web Designer, April 2013 - Jun 2013

Coding web site. Project OFY web store http://www.ofy.rs



Contact vvlladimir@gmail.com Serbia: +381 60 088 08 55

EDUCATION

College of Professional Studies of Polytechnic in Belgrade BEOGRADSKA POLITEHNIKA

Beograd, Serbia, 2006 – 2011 Graphic Designer

Electro-technical high school "Zemun"

Belgrade, Serbia, 1997 – 2001 electrician automation

SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Adobe XD Wireframes Mockups UI Design HTML CSS Javascript React js